Hey, Rex here with 2 in Oklahoma here in Dallas.
I ran into Felipe Smadje.
The Spanish trials rider.
That's right.
You may have seen these guys on America's Got Talent.
How long have you guys been riding?
We've been riding since we were around 10 or 11, so about 13 or 14 years.
Wow, okay.
Going to town for quite a while now, but to ride trials, it takes that long to even ride the bike.
Exactly.
It takes a long time, but once you get to that level, it's one of the most fun sports you can do.
It is a lot of fun.
It's great exercise, too.
And I understand you guys compete, right?
Yeah, we actually, I try to compete.
My brother, he competes very well.
He's the four time national champion.
I hold my own.
I ride pro class very long with him, but usually he's at the front of the pack.
I'm just trying to beat a couple of guys.
We're both in there, though, both competing.
So what's been the reaction?
I mean, I bet all the guys, like Sherco and Gas Gas, the guys that make trials bikes,
probably just think you're the greatest thing to come along.
I mean, have you increased awareness of the sport?
Yeah, that was actually not only increased awareness of the sport,
because that was one thing that we really shoot for, because I mean, we love the sport.
We love to spread it.
That's kind of why we travel around doing demos, I mean, to bring the sport to new people.
And there's no better medium than national live television.
So not only were we able to bring and grow what we're doing in our shows and our name,
but also the sport of trials and then even motorcycle as a whole,
because it's got a very negative aspect by a lot of the world.
They think of motorcycles, they think of pollution, they think of death, they think of injury.
And by what we did, we were able to bring it into a tight, confined area,
indoor in a building in downtown L.A.
So by jumping these barriers, we were able to open some eyes and make people realize
that maybe the motorcycles aren't such a bad thing.
And so that was a really big thing that we brought from the show is a really cool
experience and to be able to open up people's eyes in that aspect was really awesome.
And you scored a gig at like the International Motorcycle Show.
And we're here after it, so you know, it was all good for sure.
So you're going to go around all 12 of them, right?
Yep, yep. We got one down two weeks ago in San Mateo.
We're here in Dallas, Texas.
It was a while getting here. We had some transmission issues.
Oh, really?
I mean, still haven't slept since we left to leave here two days ago.
So we're running on thin right now.
It's like you're really a rock star.
Yeah, that's what that feels like.
Oh, cool.
In that case, wow.
Well, there's some other things that go along with that, too.
Yeah, so it's been really good.
We're going to do the whole series and we've really been able to get our name out there
and we're booking more shows and, you know, we're doing what we really want to do,
which is entertain people on our bikes.
You know, that's what we've been working for years to be able to do.
And now that we have that ability and, you know, the option to do it.
Right. We're pushing for what you love for a living.
What a great idea.
Well, we're going to go have a seat and watch the show.
And I wish you luck, man.
Hey, thanks a lot. Enjoy the show.
We need somebody to jump over this guy in.
Thanks a lot, man. Nice to meet you, Phil.
Thank you for watching.
Come on over to the tent, get some autographs for these guys.
We've got some free posters for you.
Get some of these awesome goat shirts we've got.
Give these guys a high five.
Give them a handshake. They're tired.